https://www.bryant-unlimited.co.uk/privacy_and_cookies.html

Exhibitions
Where are we?
My Account
New Product:     IEC Lock+ Rewireable Cable Plugs. Click here to view this product.
New Product:     B&W International Outdoor Cases for GoPro and DJI OSMO. Click here to view this product.
New Product:     Cable Bridges with integral lids . Click here to view this product.
New Product:     Korus '12G' BNC Cable Crimp Plugs. Click here to view this product.
New Product:     eyePower MDU. The most intelligent MDU in the world - ever! Click here to view this product.
New Product:     Dimmable LED Script Lights. Click here to view this product.
NB. We are currently facing an unprecedented number of cost price increases from suppliers and the frequency of these means that keeping prices accurate on our website is difficult. We will always try to minimise the effects of supplier increases by buying in volume, but inevitably some selling prices will have to increase from those shown. Please contact our sales team for an accurate quotation whilst our website is updated. We apologise in advance for any inconvenience.
About Us  Privacy and Cookies
Bryant Unlimited Privacy Notice
Version 1 – (May 18th 2018 - Bryant Unlimited)
Bryant Unlimited collects data from visitors throughout the website experience. This is largely to provide interactive functionality that would otherwise be impossible without collecting the minimum amount of data. Some data is also used to analyse your experience anonymously to improve the website experience.
Bryant Unlimited respects your privacy so we will not sell your data to third parties, allow any access to the data that isn’t necessary to honour any other contracts we have in place or store excessive amounts of data we no longer need.
Bryant Unlimited will comply with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) (EU May 25th 2018).
Definitions
Data Subject – any living person.
Third Party – another company who Bryant Unlimited works with to provide services to the Data Subject.
Personally Identifiable Information – data belonging to the Data Subject that can be used to uniquely identify them.
Data Controller – any organisation that stores Personally Identifiable Information, e.g. Bryant Unlimited.
Data Processor – any organisation that works on (processes) Personally Identifiable Information.
How we obtain your data
Bryant Unlimited collects data from the Data Subject during the use of this website. Some of that data may be Personally Identifiable Information. This may be entered into web forms or provided to the website by the browser (such as IP address).
Bryant Unlimited may also obtain Personally Identifiable Information about the Data Subject from a Third Party as part of a contract to work with that data.
How we use your data
Bryant Unlimited primarily uses data from the Data Subject either to serve a contract between Bryant Unlimited and the Data Subject, or to provide necessary functionality on this website.
Bryant Unlimited may also collect additional data to satisfy other legal requirements, such as is required for e-commerce.
Third Parties which have access to the data collected
Bryant Unlimited works with several Third Parties to provide the service the Data Subject receives.
In all cases there is either an explicit contract in place between Bryant Unlimited and the Third Party, Terms and Conditions or another legally binding relationship.
The data will likely be shared with:
Alphabet Inc (Google) – a suite of Google Tools is used by Bryant Unlimited.
Intergage Ltd – website host/provider.
The data is also rarely shared with the following:
Mobile phones – our staff may enter your contact number into their phones for the purpose of a meeting and will then erase the number after the meeting.
Marketing
Bryant Unlimited does not share your data with any Third Parties for marketing purposes unless the Data Subject has explicitly opted in.
Necessary Cookies
Bryant Unlimited uses a couple of cookies for the correct operation of this web site and cannot be disabled. These cookies have the prefix c2copybryantunlimited.
Third Party Cookies
Bryant Unlimited can mostly operate without the use of third-party cookies. Third-party cookies will not be used unless the Data Subject has explicitly opted in.
Bryant Unlimited will not add social sharing buttons to the page unless the Data Subject has explicitly opted in to social cookies.
Bryant Unlimited will not include any tracking systems unless the Data Subject has explicitly opted in to tracking cookies.
Bryant Unlimited will allow Google Analytics to operate on this website in order to provide necessary anonymous analytical data. This may result in a small amount of Personally Identifiable Information being collected but this is only used as statistics and not for identification purposes. These cookies have the prefix __utm.
Data Security and Storage
Bryant Unlimited will store data for only as long as necessary to fulfil the purpose for which it was obtained. Some data may be held for longer if it is either held on other systems that have not been updated, in backup data that has not expired or because of another lawful basis.
Bryant Unlimited takes security seriously and makes use of technology where feasible to secure data and protect against breaches.
Personal data protection principles
We adhere to the principles relating to processing of Personal Data set out in the GDPR (as follows) which require Personal Data to be:
(a)
processed lawfully, fairly and in a transparent manner (Lawfulness, Fairness and Transparency)
(b)
collected only for specified, explicit and legitimate purposes (Purpose Limitation)
(c)
adequate, relevant and limited to what is necessary in relation to the purposes for which it is processed (Data Minimisation)
(d)
accurate and where necessary kept up to date (Accuracy)
(e)
not kept in a form which permits identification of Data Subjects for longer than is necessary for the purposes for which the data is processed (Storage Limitation)
(f)
processed in a manner that ensures its security using appropriate technical and organisational measures to protect against unauthorised or unlawful processing and against accidental loss, destruction or damage (Security, Integrity and Confidentiality)
(g)
not transferred to another country without appropriate safeguards being in place (Transfer Limitation)
(h)
made available to Data Subjects and Data Subjects allowed to exercise certain rights in relation to their Personal Data (Data Subject's Rights and Requests)
Data Subject's rights and requests
Data Subjects have rights when it comes to how Bryant Unlimited handles their Personal Data. These include rights to:
(a)
withdraw consent to processing at any time
(b)
receive certain information about the Data Controller's Processing activities
(c)
request access to their personal data that we hold
(d)
prevent our use of their personal data for direct marketing purposes
(e)
ask us to erase personal data if it is no longer necessary in relation to the purposes for which it was collected or processed or to rectify inaccurate data or to complete incomplete data
(f)
restrict processing in specific circumstances
(g)
challenge processing which has been justified on the basis of our legitimate interests or in the public interest
(h)
object to decisions based solely on automated processing, including profiling (ADM)
(i)
prevent processing that is likely to cause damage or distress to the Data Subject or anyone else
(j)
be notified of a personal data breach which is likely to result in high risk to their rights and freedoms
(k)
make a complaint to the supervisory authority
(l)
receive or ask for their personal data to be transferred to a third party in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format.
Updates to our Privacy Notice
This Privacy Notice will be reviewed regularly and this page will be updated with changes.
Contacting the Data Protection Officer (DPO)
If you have any concerns about how Personally Identifiable Information is used by Bryant Unlimited please contact the Data Protection Officer:
Graham Tottle                                                                        graham.tottle@bryant-unlimited.co.uk
Bryant Unlimited                                                                  +44 (0)20 8404 4050
I can't find it!
Exhibitions
Newsletter
© Copyright 2020 Bryant Unlimited | Site Map | Contact | Privacy | Terms and Conditions
Connect with us
E&OE
Powered by Intergage
